// Questions provided by https://www.usefultrivia.com/science_trivia/ for the most part.  I edited some of them a bit

var myQuiz = [
    {
        question: "What physicist discovered that a wave's frequency changes when the source and the observer are in motion relative to one another?",
        choices: ["Charles Doppler", "Albert Einstein", "Enrico Fermi", "Max Planck"],
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "Who invented the first battery?",
        choices: ["Nikola Tesla", "Alessandro Volta", "Benjamin Franklin", "Luigi Galvani"],
        answer: "2"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is considered the founder of the modern science of genetics?",
        choices: ["Gregor Mendel", "Dmitri Mendeleev", "Ernest Rutherford", "Francis Crick"],
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "What cosmologist formulated a heliocentric cosmology?",
        choices: ["Galileo Galilei", "Archimedes", "Isaac Newton", "Nicolaus Copernicus"],
        answer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "Who wrote the first algorithm intended to be carried out by a machine?",
        choices: ["Alan Turing", "Marvin Minsky", "Claude Shannon", "Ada Lovelace"],
        answer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "What theoretical physicist and cosmologist suffered from Lou Gehrig's disease?",
        choices: ["Carl Sagan", "Neil DeGrasse Tyson", "Stephen Hawking", "Albert Einstein"],
        answer: "3"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is 'The Science Guy'?",
        choices: ["Carl Sagan", "Bill Nye", "Ross Geller", "Steve Irwin"],
        answer: "2"
    },
    {
        question: "What scientist's book laid the foundations for classical mechanics?",
        choices: ["Nicolaus Copernicus", "Michael Faraday", "Galileo Galilei", "Isaac Newton"],
        answer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: "What scientist wrote Mysterium Cosmographicum?",
        choices: ["Galileo Galilei", "Isaac Newton", "Johannes Kepler", "Nicolaus Copernicus"],
        answer: "3"
    },
    {
        question: "What scientist is famous for the discovery of the elements polonium and radium?",
        choices: ["Marie Curie", "Dmitri Mendeleev", "Robert Bunsen", "Alfred Nobel"],
        answer: "1"
    },
];